

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Front-end developer based in Orange County, California, specialized in designing and building websites and full-stack web apps. I have 1 year of experience working with clients to develop and transform their ideas to real-world application to satisfy their consumer's needs. Still learning and growing to improve my current skills

SKILLS

HTML . CSS . JavaScript . jQuery . Express . AJAX . Node . Angular . Python . Django . MySQL . C# . ASP.NET . Adobe Illustrator . Adobe XD . Adobe Photoshop

CONTACT

Mobile: 949.381.9867
Email: rolandolopantzi@gmail.com
Portfolio: rolandolopantzi.com
Github: github.com/RoLo-dev
LinkedIn: @rolandolopantzi

WORK HISTORY

Logistics Coordinator & Designer

Expert Coatings & Graphics (Sept 2018 - Nov 2019)

- Inspect and prepare raw material to process to avoid any hold ups
- Inventory control of all raw material that we have for each customer
- Oversee artwork gets printed correctly, manipulate colors and dimensions for a clean print

Graphic Designer

Technaprint (May 2015 - Aug 2018)

- Provide proofs/mock ups based on client products with various artwork
- Redraw or create artwork or logos if client did not have artwork needed for marketing purposes
- Multitask working with phone and computer even with multiple clients
- Inspect artwork gets outputted correctly for screen, plate material and on final product

Translator & Customer Service

State Farm Insurance (Aug 2014 - May 2015)

- Provide good communication skills both in english and in spanish
- Multitask working with phone and computer even with multiple clients
- -Taking payments mostly, credit card payments
- Scheduling appointments with clients

EDUCATION

Coding Dojo - Full Stack Development Nov 2019 - Feb 2020 Orange Coast College - General Studies Aug 2011 - May 2012 Newport Harbor High School - Diploma Sept 2006 June 2010